http://www.northshorebank.com/privacy.aspx

Skip to main content.
Money Market Accounts
Certificates of Deposit (CDs)
Business Bill Pay
Remote Deposit Capture (RDC)
Our Commitment to You
Your trust is the cornerstone of our relationship. We understand that you have entrusted us with your private financial information and we do everything we can to maintain that trust. That is why we work diligently to safeguard your privacy and the information you provide us; whether in person, over the phone, or via the Internet.
Children's Privacy Policy Statement
Protecting children on the Internet is very important to us. We do not knowingly collect, use or maintain any information through our websites about children who are under the age of 13. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) protects children under the age of 13 from the online collection of personal information.
Cookies/Online Services Privacy Statement
We may collect information about you and about your device when you visit our websites or use our online services. We may collect this information when you open an account, log-in and use online services, schedule an appointment, or contact us from our websites or through online services. We use this information to verify and authenticate you (for some services), protect against fraud and other security risks, communicate with you, and as otherwise permitted by law. In general, we and our third-party providers and advertisers use cookies and other technologies to optimize the functionality of our websites, to help us understand how our websites are used and to provide users with interest-based content or advertising based upon their browsing activities and interests.
We use commercially reasonable procedures and various technical, administrative and physical safeguards to help protect the confidentiality of your personal information. However, no data transmitted over the Internet or stored or maintained by us or our third-party service providers can be 100% secure given the reality of communication via technology systems. Therefore, although we believe the measures implemented by us are commercially reasonable and reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved, we do not promise or guarantee that your personal information or private communications sent to us over those systems will always remain private or secure. Personal identifying information, for example your account number or Taxpayer Identification Number, should only be shared in a secure manner. We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security features.
By using our websites and/or the online services, and providing us with personal information, you agree to the practices described above and in the Privacy Policy and to the updates to such terms and such policy posted here from time to time.
Notice to California Residents
North Shore Bank does not do business in California and is therefore not subject to the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA"). However, the CCPA provides consumers with specific rights regarding the collection, use, disclosure, and sale of their Personal Information. We will continue to closely monitor the developments under the CCPA and if, at any time, we believe we may be subject to the CCPA, we will updated our privacy policy accordingly. We will not share your personal information except as permitted by law. To ensure you stay informed of all changes, you should check this page and our privacy policies periodically.
Still have questions?
Contact us with additional questions: Email
|
877-672-2265
